// The "||" notation doesn't work yet
Fixtures = typeof Fixtures !== "undefined" ? Fixtures : {};

Fixtures.questions = [
    {
        "category": "8",
        "question": "~~8-0 is the obscure emoticon that stands for _____.",
        "answer": "BAD HAIR DAY"
    },
    {
        "category": "107",
        "question": "Monroe Isadore, a 107-year-old man from Arkansas, died during a _____.",
        "answer": "SHOOTOUT"
    },
    {
        "category": "55000",
        "question": "Owning 55,000 of them, Ted Turner has the world's largest private collection of _____.",
        "answer": "BISON"
    },
    {
        "category": "5% MORE MILK",
        "question": "A study published in the journal Anthrozoo reported that cows produce 5% more milk when they are given _____.",
        "answer": "NAMES"
    },
    {
        "category": "AFGHANISTAN",
        "question": "In 2002, Bruce Willis sent 12,000 boxes of _____ to U.S. soldiers in Afghanistan.",
        "answer": "GIRL SCOUT COOKIES"
    },
    {
        "category": "ALFRED",
        "question": "The electric chair was invented by a professional _____ named Alfred Southwick.",
        "answer": "DENTIST"
    },
    {
        "category": "ARRESTED",
        "question": "A man in L.A. was arrest at a police-sponsored gun buyback when, instead of a gun, he tried to sell the cops a _____.",
        "answer": "PIPE BOMB"
    },
    {
        "category": "BAD",
        "question": "CELEBRITY TWEET! 9:43 PM - 1 Oct 13 @MikeTyson tweeted, \"I'm a bad ____.:",
        "answer": "BOWLER"
    },
    {
        "category": "BALLS",
        "question": "Only about 14 games were ever made for the Gizmondo game system including the game \"_____ Balls.\"",
        "answer": "STICKY"
    },
    {
        "category": "BLOWING",
        "question": "On November 12, 1970, George Thornton, a highwat engineer in Oregon, had the unusual job of blowing up a _____.",
        "answer": "DEAD WHALE"
    },
    {
        "category": "BOATS",
        "question": "People in Damariscotta, Maine hold an annual race where they use _____ as boats.",
        "answer": "PUMPKINS"
    },
    {
        "category": "BOXING",
        "question": "Leo Granit Kraft is a world champion in an unusual sport that combines boxing and _____.",
        "answer": "CHESS"
    },
    {
        "category": "BRANSON",
        "question": "Andrew Wilson, a man from Branson, Missouri, legally changed his name to simply _____.",
        "answer": "THEY"
    },
    {
        "category": "BUENOS AIRES",
        "question": "As a young student in Buenos Aires, Pope Francis worked as a _____.",
        "answer": "BOUNCER"
    },
    {
        "category": "BUTTOCKS",
        "question": "Dasypygal is an adjective meaning \"having _____ buttocks.\"",
        "answer": "HAIRY"
    },
    {
        "category": "CALLUS",
        "question": "A woman in Muncie, Indiana was hospitalized after trying to remove a callus on her foot with a _____.",
        "answer": "SHOTGUN"
    },
    {
        "category": "CALVARY",
        "question": "Sponsored by the Calvary Lutheran Church, people in Fort Worth Texas can now attend the unconventional Church-in-a-_____.",
        "answer": "PUB"
    },
    {
        "category": "CHARLES BUKOWSKI",
        "question": "Famed American poet Charles Bukowski's tombstone is engraved with the words \"Don't _____.\"",
        "answer": "TRY"
    },
    {
        "category": "CRUISES",
        "question": "Jacobite Cruises purchased unusual insurance to protect it from damage caused by _____.",
        "answer": "THE LOCH NESS MONSTER"
    },
    {
        "category": "DEVIL",
        "question": "El Colacho is a Spanish festival where people dress up like the devil and jump over _____.",
        "answer": "BABIES"
    },
    {
        "category": "DIRTY",
        "question": "Utah's Lehi City Council approved a request to change the name of _____ Road because it sounded sort of dirty.",
        "answer": "MORNING GLORY"
    },
    {
        "category": "DRESSES",
        "question": "Cheap Chic Weddings is an annual contest in which participants make wedding dresses out of _____.",
        "answer": "TOILET PAPER"
    },
    {
        "category": "DUCK",
        "question": "Marcella Hazan is the culinary guru who pioneered the unusual technique of cooking duck with a _____.",
        "answer": "HAIR DRYER"
    },
    {
        "category": "E.T.",
        "question": "The sound of E.T. walking was made by someone squishing _____.",
        "answer": "JELL-O"
    },
    {
        "category": "EBAY",
        "question": "The first item listed on eBay was a broken _____.",
        "answer": "LASER POINTER"
    },
    {
        "category": "EINSTEIN",
        "question": "Oddly enough, Albert Einstein's eyeballs can be found in a _____ in New York City.",
        "answer": "SAFE DEPOSIT BOX"
    },
    {
        "category": "ERECTED",
        "question": "In 2013, a wealthy Michagan man bought the house next to his ex -wife and erected a giant bronze statue of a _____.",
        "answer": "MIDDLE FINGER"
    },
    {
        "category": "FACIAL",
        "question": "For $180, the Shizuka New York skin care salon offeres the unusual but traditional Japanese facial that is part rice bran and part _____.",
        "answer": "BIRD POOP"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The shape of wombat poop.",
        "answer": "CUBE"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "What the British call the dance that Americans call the \"Hokey Pokey.\"",
        "answer": "HOKEY COKEY"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The band Queen's original name.",
        "answer": "SMILE"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The name of the first chimp sent into space.",
        "answer": "HAM"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The name for a group of porcupines.",
        "answer": "PRICKLE"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The name of the dog that won the 2012 World's Ugliest Dog Competition.",
        "answer": "MUGLY"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "Dr. Suess is credit with coining this common derogatory term in his 1950 book If I Ran the Zoo.",
        "answer": "NERD"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "Harry Houdini once threatened to shoot all of these people.",
        "answer": "PSYCHICS"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The original name for the search engine that became Google.",
        "answer": "BACKRUB"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "Miley Cyrus's real first name.",
        "answer": "DESTINY"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The name of the dildo resembling Queen Elizabeth II that's sold by the Company Masturpieces.",
        "answer": "BUCKINGHAM PHALLUS"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "Michael J. Fox's middle name.",
        "answer": "ANDREW"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The name of the Star Trek starship in creator Gene Roddenberry's original script.",
        "answer": "YORKTOWN"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "At 65% alcohol by volume, Brewmesiter brews the world's strongest beer, which goes by this name.",
        "answer": "ARMAGEDDOM"
    },
    {
        "category": "FINAL FIBBAGE",
        "question": "The name of the man on the Quaker Oats label.",
        "answer": "LARRY"
    },
    {
        "category": "FIRE",
        "question": "During a famous fire in 1567, a Norwegian man named Hans Steininger died after tripping over a _____.",
        "answer": "BEARD"
    },
    {
        "category": "FISHING",
        "question": "The fishing company E21 makes a very peculiar fishing rod that is composed of 70% _____.",
        "answer": "CARROTS"
    },
    {
        "category": "FLIGHT",
        "question": "The first reporting on the Wright .rothers' flights appeared not in a newspaper or on radio, but in a small journal dedicated to the topic of _____.",
        "answer": "BEEKEEPING"
    },
    {
        "category": "FOOD",
        "question": "There's a novelty museum in Arlington, Massachusetts that only collects food that has been _____.",
        "answer": "BURNT"
    },
    {
        "category": "GALLAGHER",
        "question": "Prop comic Gallagher, known for smashing watermelons with a sledgehammer, earned a college degree in the field of _____.",
        "answer": "CHEMICAL ENGINEERING"
    },
    {
        "category": "GANG",
        "question": "In 1976 boxing legend Muhammad Ali released an education children's album titled \"Ali and His Gang Vs. Mr. _____.\"",
        "answer": "TOOTH DECAY"
    },
    {
        "category": "GIFT",
        "question": "On January 13, 2014, U.S. Secretary of State John Kerry presented to Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrow the odd gift of two very large _____.",
        "answer": "POTATOES"
    },
    {
        "category": "GIN",
        "question": "In the 16th century, gin was referred to as the Mother's _____.",
        "answer": "RUIN"
    },
    {
        "category": "GLASTONBURY",
        "question": "During th mid to late-nineties, the English town of Glastonbury was on a manhunt for the old house intruder known as \"The _____.\"",
        "answer": "TICKLER"
    },
    {
        "category": "GROWLERS",
        "question": "According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Association, small icebergs are offically called \"growlers.\" Medium icebergs go by the strange, two-word name \"_____.\"",
        "answer": "BERGY BITS"
    },
    {
        "category": "HIP",
        "question": "Suffering from an extremely rare side effect after getting hip surgery in 2010, a Dutch man has alienated his family because he cannot stop _____.",
        "answer": "LAUGHING"
    },
    {
        "category": "HOUR",
        "question": "It's weird work but Jackie Samuel charges $60 an hour to _____.",
        "answer": "SNUGGLE"
    },
    {
        "category": "HUGGIES",
        "question": "Huggies Brazil developed a phone app that tells you when a baby's diaper is wet. It's called _____.",
        "answer": "TWEETPEE"
    },
    {
        "category": "ICE CREAM",
        "question": "Ben and Jerry only started making ice cream because it was too expensive to make _____.",
        "answer": "BAGELS"
    },
    {
        "category": "ILLINOIS",
        "question": "A spectator in an Illinois courtroom was sentenced to six months in jail for ______ during a trial.",
        "answer": "YAWNING"
    },
    {
        "category": "ILLINOIS",
        "question": "The sports teams at Freeport High School in Illinois are oddly named after an inanimate object. The teams are called the Freeport _____.",
        "answer": "PRETZELS"
    },
    {
        "category": "INVENTOR",
        "question": "The inventor of the laxative Ex-Lax has the unusual name Max _____.",
        "answer": "KISS"
    },
    {
        "category": "IOWA",
        "question": "Britt, Iowa annually crowns a King and Queen _____.",
        "answer": "HOBO"
    },
    {
        "category": "JAPAN",
        "question": "Tashirojima is an island off of Japan that is complete overrun by _____.",
        "answer": "CATS"
    },
    {
        "category": "JOHN LARROQUETTE",
        "question": "For his voiceover work in Texas Chainsaw Massacre, John Larroqueet was paid not with money, but with _____.",
        "answer": "MARIJUANA"
    },
    {
        "category": "JOSH",
        "question": "The fans of musician Josh Groban are called _____.",
        "answer": "GROBANITES"
    },
    {
        "category": "JOY",
        "question": "Jim Begelow, Ph.D., wrote a book called The Joy of Un_____!.",
        "answer": "CIRCUMCISING"
    },
    {
        "category": "JUNO",
        "question": "While president of the United States, John Adams had a dog named Juno and a dog named _____.",
        "answer": "SATAN"
    },
    {
        "category": "KICKSTARTER",
        "question": "A Kickstarter campaign met its $30,000 goal on April 7, 2012 for its shoes designed fo _____.",
        "answer": "ATHEISTS"
    },
    {
        "category": "KILL",
        "question": "In 2007, Golden Laurel Entertainment published a violent board game called Kill the _____.",
        "answer": "HIPPIES"
    },
    {
        "category": "LICK",
        "question": "In 2012, a 26-year-old man from London went on a mission to lick every _____ in the United Kingdom.",
        "answer": "CATHEDRAL"
    },
    {
        "category": "MARYLAND",
        "question": "Maryland's official state sport is _____.",
        "answer": "JOUSTING"
    },
    {
        "category": "MOROCCO",
        "question": "In 2003, Morocco made the highly unusual offer to send 2,000 _____ to assist the United States' war efforts in Iraq.",
        "answer": "MONKEYS"
    },
    {
        "category": "MUSSOLINI",
        "question": "Romano Mussolini, son of the fascist dictator Benito Mussolini, did not follow in his father's footsteps. Instead, he made his living as a _____.",
        "answer": "JAZZ MUSICIAN"
    },
    {
        "category": "MUSTACHE",
        "question": "Patented in 1890, U.S. Patent US435748 is for a mustache ____.",
        "answer": "GUARD"
    },
    {
        "category": "NEBRASKA",
        "question": "In 2007, to make a point, Nebraskain State Sen. Ernie Chambers filed a frivolous lawsuit against _____.",
        "answer": "GOD"
    },
    {
        "category": "NEPAL",
        "question": "ROAD TRIP! When in Nepal, visit the village of Parsawa and Laxmipur, where you can enjoy the slightly off-putting 10 day _____ Festival.",
        "answer": "CURSING"
    },
    {
        "category": "NEW HAMPSHIRE",
        "question": "A group known as the \"Robin Hooders\" in Keene, New Hampshire pay for other people's _____.",
        "answer": "PARKING METERS"
    },
    {
        "category": "NORWAY",
        "question": "In an effort to push \"slow TV,\" Norway had a 12-hour block of programming in 2013 dedicated to _____.",
        "answer": "KNITTING"
    },
    {
        "category": "OH",
        "question": "Belmont University in Nashville has offered a class called \"Oh, Look, a _____.\"",
        "answer": "CHICKEN"
    },
    {
        "category": "PACIFIC",
        "question": "The area in the Pacific Ocean where great white sharks congregate every spring is called the White Shark _____.",
        "answer": ""
    },
    {
        "category": "PANTS",
        "question": "Reg Mellor is the reigning champion of a sport that just involves keeping a _____ in your pants.",
        "answer": "FERRET"
    },
    {
        "category": "PEPSI",
        "question": "During the summer of 2007, Pepsi sold a gree-tinted coal in Japan called Pepsi Ice _____.",
        "answer": "CUCUMBER"
    },
    {
        "category": "PETER",
        "question": "Under Peter the Great, noblemen had to pay 100 rubles a year for a _____ license.",
        "answer": "BEARD"
    },
    {
        "category": "PETITION",
        "question": "In 2000, Australia had its larget ever online petition, which called for an end to rising _____ prices.",
        "answer": "BEER"
    },
    {
        "category": "PIGS",
        "question": "Although very unconventional, farmer William von Schneidau feeds his pigs _____.",
        "answer": "MARIJUANA"
    },
    {
        "category": "PILE",
        "question": "When Paul Nelson and Andrew Hunter climbed Britain's highest mountain in 2006, they made an unusual discovery hidden behind a pile of stones. It was a _____.",
        "answer": "PIANO"
    },
    {
        "category": "POLICE",
        "question": "At 2:45 a.m. one day in June 2013, a man in Orlando, Florida was arrested for walking up to a police officer and punching his _____.",
        "answer": "HORSE"
    },
    {
        "category": "POPE PIUS II",
        "question": "Before he became pope, Pope Pius II wrote an erotic novel titled The Tale of the _____.",
        "answer": "TWO LOVERS"
    },
    {
        "category": "PRIZE",
        "question": "A 2013 Pakistani game show caused a controversy when their grand prize was a _____.",
        "answer": "BABY"
    },
    {
        "category": "PROM",
        "question": "In 2013, two teens from Sequoyah High Sxhool near Atlanta, Georgia won $5,0000 schoplarships for wearing _____ to prom",
        "answer": "DUCT TAPE"
    },
    {
        "category": "QUEENS",
        "question": "Since 2000, a couple in Queens, New York has been living rent-free in a _____ in exchange for taking care of it.",
        "answer": "CEMETERY"
    },
    {
        "category": "RATHER",
        "question": "For a story he was reporting on in 1955, Dan Rather tried _____ for the first time.",
        "answer": "HEROIN"
    },
    {
        "category": "RECKONING",
        "question": "Chosen, Shunned and Reckoning are all books in an unusual series about _____ vampires.",
        "answer": "AMISH"
    },
    {
        "category": "RELEASE",
        "question": "In 2013, a 51-year-old Swedish inmate broke out of prison a day before his scheduled release so he could go see a _____.",
        "answer": "DENTIST"
    },
    {
        "category": "RIOT",
        "question": "There is a riot police unit in the Russian town of Rostov-na-Donu that is comprised entirely of _____'",
        "answer": "TWINS"
    },
    {
        "category": "SADDAM",
        "question": "In 1980, Saddam Hussein was named an honorary citizen of _____.",
        "answer": "DETROIT"
    },
    {
        "category": "SEIZURES",
        "question": "A neurology professor at Albany Medical College documented in a 1991 medical journal that one of his patients had seizures when she heard _____.",
        "answer": "MARY HART'S VOICE"
    },
    {
        "category": "SEX",
        "question": "In 2008, a couple was killed in South Africa while having sex on a _____.",
        "answer": "RAILROAD TRACK"
    },
    {
        "category": "SIMMONS",
        "question": "CELEBRITY TWEET! 2:49 PM - 15 Nov 13 Richard Simmons' Twitter handle @TheWeightSaint tweeted: \"At the airport ____ everyone.\"",
        "answer": "HUGGING"
    },
    {
        "category": "SMUGGLE",
        "question": "In 2010, Customs officers on the Morway-Sweden border intercepted a truck trying to smuggle 28 tons of _____ from China.",
        "answer": "GARLIC"
    },
    {
        "category": "STABBED",
        "question": "In 2012, a teenager from Weslaco, Texas claimed the reason he stabbed his friend was because a _____ made him do it.",
        "answer": "OUIJA BOARD"
    }
];
